Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
  - Chatham Manufacturing Company
    - Chatham blankets
      - Interviews with buyers in N.Y. department stores, 1929 June
      - Investigation in department stores in cities of 25,000 or over, 1931 May
  - Chesebrough Manufacturing Company
    - Trend of sales of Chesebrough products (5 years), 1936 Aug.
    - Drug and variety store business in 94 metropolitan districts, 1937 Apr.
    - Colgate-Palmolive survey, 1937 Apr.
    - Survey on uses, frequency and remedies of Vaseline, 1937 Apr.
    - Office investigation on eye makeup, 1937 June
    - Investigation on use of Vaseline for the hands, 1937 Oct.
    - Survey on use of remedies for dry scalp, 1938 Mar.
    - Dealer survey on recognition of radio program (See reel #283 for 1926 investigation), 1938 Mar.
  - City Baking Company
    - Results of bread tests, 1934 Sept.
    - Consumer and dealer survey on bread and other bakery products in Baltimore and place, 1936 July
    - Consumer and dealer survey on bread and other bakery products in Newark, 1936 Aug.
    - Comparison of consumer surveys--Baltimore vs. Newark, 1936 Sept.
  - J&J Colman Ltd.
    - Sale and use of dry mustard--Chicago, 1924 June
    - Office investigation use of mustard in homes, 1924 July
    - Dealer investigation 7 cities, 1924 July
    - Investigation among jobbers (Nationwide), 1924 July
    - Investigation among druggists in N.Y., 1924 Dec.
    - Dealer interviews, 1925 Sept.
    - Grocers investigation Albany and Schenectady, 1927 Mar.
    - Dealer investigation--Newark, 1927 Apr.
    - Grocer markets, 1928 Aug.
    - Consumer investigation, 1928 Sept.
    - Dealer investigation New York, 1928 Sept.
    - Mail investigation, 1924 Sept.
    - Office investigation on bath salts, 1928 Oct.
    - Hardness of water in U.S., 1928 Nov.
    - Analysis of spice imports, 1929 Oct.
    - Colman's mustard copy platform, 1930
  - Corning Glass Works
    - Pyrex pre examination in N.Y., 1925 Apr.
    - Office investigation refrigerator dishes, 1925 Aug.
    - Nursing bottles--Minnesota (baby bottles investigation), 1925 Aug.
    - Pyrex nursing bottles investigation and try outs Pennsylvania and Mass., N.Y., Ill., 1925 Sept.
    - Pyrex nursing bottles investigation and try outs--White Plains, 1925 Oct.
    - Mail investigation on nursing bottles, 1925 Nov.
    - Mail investigation on baking dishes, 1925 Oct.
    - Pyrex consumer and dealer investigation Poughkeepsie, 1925 Aug.
    - Pyrex consumer investigation Jamaica, Long Island, 1925 June
    - Pyrex consumer investigation, 1925 Aug.
    - Pyrex consumer investigation, 1925 Sept.
    - Population and no of stores in 205 jobbing areas, 1925 Feb.
    - Ultra-violet glass in hospitals--Report, 1928 Aug.
    - Pyrex investigation, 1926 Aug.
    - Pyrex nursing bottles--doctor's questionnaires, 1939 Sept.
    - Pyrex nursing bottles investigation among doctors, 1926 Dec.
    - Pyrex nursing bottles doctor's questionnaires, 1925 May
    - Pyrex nursing bottles questionnaires to doctors, 1929 Dec.
    - Pyrex ovenware investigation, 1930 Jan.
    - Report of labeling products similar to Pyrex, 1930 Apr.
    - Consumer investigation on chinaware, 1930 Dec.
    - Pyrex investigation, 1930 Nov.
    - Estimate of total ovenware business in U.S., 1931 Sept.
    - Facts of price reduction policy, 1932 Mar.
    - Investigation of kitchenware sales--N.Y. department stores, 1933 June
    - Experience with price maintenance, 1934 Aug.
    - Competitive investigation on Pyrex, 1934 Oct.
    - Consumer investigation on Pyrex, 1935 Jan.
    - Plan for nationwide consumer investigation of Pyrex, 1935 Oct.
  - Curtis Publishing Company
    - Market for the Ladies Home Journal, 1933 Dec.
    - Attitude toward the Ladies Home Journal, 1934 Oct.
    - McCall's promotion piece--Office investigation, 1936 Sept.
    - Ladies Home Journal promotion piece--Office investigation, 1937 Mar.
  - Northam Warren Corporation
    - Cutex
      - Report on shopping for Cutex, 1923 Apr.
      - Department stores handling toilet articles and drug sundries (US and Canada), 1923
      - Drug trade information, 1923 Dec.
      - Investigation on manicure sticks, 1923
      - Report on 3 weeks demonstration at A&S building, 1921 Sept.
      - Memo on investigation at Gimbel's on Cutex, 1921 Apr.
      - Memo on investigation at Macy's on Cutex, 1921 June
      - Memo on investigation on trip on Cutex, 1921 May
      - Cutex powder polis container, 1921 Apr.
      - Drug trade and relationship to advertised merchandise, 1922 Dec.
      - Expenditure for furniture and house furnishings and expenditure for misc., items purchased by average working men's family in one year, 1922 Nov.
      - Notes on shopping for a cuticle cream, 1923 Aug.
      - Reports on 2 weeks sales experience at Bloomingdale's and other stores, 1923 Dec.
      - Reports on Cutex demonstrations, 1921 Aug.
      - Reports on visit to stores, 1923 Dec.
      - Reports on interviews, 1923 July
      - Reports on meeting on Cutex, 1923 May
      - Question of liquid polish, 1921
      - Investigation of Cutex nail polishes, 1921 Mar.
      - Report on Cutex liquid polish, 1920 Dec.
      - Report of conference, 1921 Apr.
      - Office investigation nail white, 1920 May
      - Charts, 1919-1921
      - Cutex mail investigation, 1923 May
      - Cutex complaints, 1922 Dec.
      - Cutex history, 1916 May
      - Memos, [1919-1921]
      - Cutex investigation, 1925 May
      - Report on manicures, 1923
      - Cutex mail investigation, 1925
      - Vanity case report, 1927 July
      - Suggestions, 1928 Apr.
      - Memos, 1926
      - Investigation, 1925-1928 (Reel 39)
  - Danderine
    - Investigation, 1933 Feb.-May
  - Eastman Kodak Company
    - Investigation, 1930-1933
  - Foremost Dairy Products, Inc.
    - Investigation, 1930-1929
  - Financial Advertising
    - Investigation, 1930-1935
  - R.T. French Company.
    - Investigation, 1929-1934
  - General Cigar Company, Inc.
    - Investigation, 1932-1936
  - B.F. Goodrich Rubber Company
    - Investigation (See also reel #196 for Dec. 28 consumer and dealer report on women's galoshes), 1928-1932 (Reel 45)
  - Gorham Company
    - Investigation, 1936 Mar.-May
  - Goodyear
    - Investigation, 1936-1938
  - Hathaway Bakeries, Inc.
    - Investigation, 1928-1931
  - Insurance
    - Investigation, 1934
    - Basic problems of fire insurance, 1931-1932
  - Andrew Jergens Co.
    - Woodbury's soap surveys and Jergen's lotion
      - Investigation, 1922-1933
      - Investigation (continued from reel 45), 1933-1936 (Reel 46)
  - Johns-Manville Company
    - Investigation, 1927-1933
  - Kops brothers, Inc.
    - Nemo corsets, 1924-1934
  - A.C. Krumm and Sons
    - Macaroni, 1926
  - Phoenix-Kraft cheese Company
    - Investigation, 1924-1935
  - La Gerardine, Inc.
    - Investigation, 1929-1930
  - Laundry problems
    - Investigation, 1921-1925
  - Lever Brothers Company
    - Miscellaneous
      - Investigation, 1921-1925
      - Investigation (continued from reel 46), 1925-1932 (Reel 47)
    - Rinso, Lux
      - Consumer investigation in Danbury, Conn. and Oshkosh, Wis. (See reel #251 for a few more investigation), 1925 July
      - Mail investigation, 1925 Aug.
      - Dealer investigation N.Y. City (Lux), 1926 Feb.
      - consumer investigation Oshkosh, etc., 1926 July
      - Mail investigations, 1926 July
      - Lux consumer investigation--Mail, 1926 Aug.
      - Lux consumer investigation--Mail, 1927 Aug.
      - Lux consumer investigation--Mail, 1927 Oct.
      - Lux toilet soap, 1927 Jan.
      - Lux, 1927 June
      - Lux consumer investigation and mail, 1928 Aug.
      - Lux consumer investigation and mail, 1928 Oct.
      - Lux consumer investigation and mail, 1929 Feb.
      - Office investigation Lux, 1929 May
      - Office report--Lux, 1929 Aug.
      - Lux investigation, 1929 Sept.
      - Lux investigation, 1929 Oct.
      - Lux investigation, 1931 July
      - Office investigation--Skin--Soap, 1932 Jan.
      - Consumer--What type garment wash, 1932 Mar.
      - Soaps--Department stores, 1932 Mar.
      - Soaps--for shampoos, 1932 Apr.
      - Hosiery data and cotton wear, 1932 May
      - Test of copy appeal--House-to-house, 1932 June
      - Lux Flakes pre-Investigation, 1932 June
      - Store investigation Lux Flakes and soap prices, 1932 July
      - Office investigation Lux, 1932 Sept.
      - Knit goods Vogue report, 1932 Nov.
      - Stocking prices, 1932 Dec.
      - Various reports, 1932 Nov.
      - Various reports, 1933 Jan.
      - General data--Lux toilet soaps, 1923 or 1925
      - Mail investigation care of skin, 1923 June
      - Dealer investigation, 1926 Jan.
      - Store reports, 1926 July
      - Mail investigation, 1926 July
      - Consumer investigation, 1926 July
      - Lux Flakes--Lux toilet soap, 1930 Apr.
      - Mail--Lux toilet soap, 1926 Aug.
      - Mail--Lux toilet soap, 1927 May
      - Comments on Lux toilet soap, 1927 Aug.
      - Investigation Lux toilet soap, 1927 Nov.
      - Investigation (wrapper) Lux toilet soap, 1927 Oct.
      - Investigation dealer--Lux toilet soap, 1928 Feb.
      - Investigation mail--Lux toilet soap, 1929 June
      - Investigation N.Y.--Lux toilet soap, 1930 Jan.
      - Investigation N.Y.--Lux toilet soap, 1930 Jan.
      - Sale of Lux in Butler stores, 1926 July
      - Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1931 Mar.
      - Lux toilet soap dealer investigation, 1931 Dec.
      - Lux toilet soap consumer survey, 1932 Aug.
      - Lux toilet soap consumer survey, 1932 Oct.
      - Whispering campaigns, 1933 Feb.
      - Consumer choice of odor--Lux toilet soap and Camay, 1933 Apr.
      - Consumer investigation soap, 1934 Apr.
  - Woodbury's Facial Soap
    - Investigation (See reel #251 for a few more investigation), 1933 Sept.
  - Lever Brothers Company
    - Rinso, Lux
      - Media study--Soap and flakes (See reel #251 for a few more investigation), 1934 Aug.
      - Office investigation complexion care, 1935 Jan.
      - Analysis of consumer investigation, 1934 Apr.
      - Office test--Removal of cosmetics, 1935 July
      - Lux sales compares with index and pot
      - Markets--Analysis, 1936 Oct.
      - Urban vs. rural, 1936 Sept.
      - Lux Flakes--Advertising experience, 1936 June
      - Office investigation 4 Lux toilet soaps, 1936 June
      - Office investigation--Designs, 1936 July
      - Office investigation--Copy appeal test, 1937 Jan.
      - Office investigation--Wrapper preference, 1937 Apr.
    - Lux Toilet Soap
      - Investigation, 1923-1937
  - Libby, McNeill and Libby
    - Investigation, 1923-1930
  - Lysol Limited
    - Investigation, 1925 Oct.
  - Maxwell House C+C321offee
    - Investigation, 1927-1929
    - Media analysis, 1932 Oct.-1934 Jan.
  - Aunt Jemima Mills Company
    - Pan cake flour, 1924-1928
  - Buxton, Inc.
    - Investigation, 1924-1930
  - Carter's Ink Company
    - Investigation, 1930 (Reel 49)
  - City Baking Company
    - Investigation, 1924-1927
  - Corona
    - Investigation, 1930
  - Phoenix Hosiery Company
    - Investigation, 1931
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Chase & Sanborn
      - Investigation, 1931, 1934
    - Fleischmann's Yeast
      - Investigation, 1930-1934
  - National Biscuit Company
    - Investigation, 1923-1935
  - National Lumber Manufacturers Association
    - Investigation, 1928
  - Miscellaneous
    - Newspaper circulation study, 1929
  - New Business
    - London--21 tests made by staff of Fassett and Johnson of Jell-O and Bird's jelly, 1923 Mar.
    - London--Jell-O investigation made by London Office, 1923 Mar.
    - Corduroy material investigation, 1923 Oct.
    - Informal report on wash all machine in Rome and Utica, 1924 Jan.
    - Washer all-consumer investigation, 1924 Feb.
    - Report of office investigation on shoes, 1924 Mar.
    - Dealer investigation on shoes, 1924 Mar.
    - Heinz cider vinegar, 1924 June
    - Office investigation on greeting cards, 1924 July
    - Red wine vinegar, 1924 July
    - Office investigation on fountain pens--N.Y. and San Francisco and Chicago, 1924 Nov.
    - Office investigation on cake prepared flour, 1924 Nov.
    - Grocery dealers interviewed for Reckitt's Bluing, 1925 June
    - Office investigation on cigars, 1925 June
    - Bluing investigation (Office in Chicago), 1925 July
    - Office investigation of Woolworth (business) stores, 1925 Aug.
    - Office investigation of George Washington coffee, 1925 Sept.
    - Canisters--Dealer investigation in Manhattan and Brooklyn, New Haven, New Rochelle and White Plains, 1925 Oct.
    - Canister--Consumer field investigation, 1925 Oct.
    - Office investigation of Woolworth stores, 1925 Oct.
    - Canister report from Chicago Office, 1925 Nov.
    - Office investigation of Van Camp--Libby, McNeil and Libby, Heinz, Campbell Soup Company and Beechnut (Dealer report attached, 1925 Dec.
    - Office investigation--Grocery stores, 1925 Dec.
    - Dealer investigation--Van Heusen non-slip shoulder strap, 1925 Aug.
    - Office test of perfume, 1927 Apr.
    - Office investigation--Pale Moon, 1927 Aug.
    - Office investigation--Calsodent and O-Don-Tex toothbrush, 1927 Sept.
    - Preliminary report on Campbell's soups--Wholesale grocers, 1927 Nov.
    - Wholesale--Retail grocers and delicatessen dealers interviews--Tea balls, 1927 Nov.
    - Marketing aspects of Johns Manville, Inc., 1927 Apr.
    - Canadian dealer investigation on radios and radio tubes, 1927 Apr.
    - Office investigation--Smoking test--Cigarettes, 1927 Apr.
    - Woolworth stores survey--No of retail food outlet Indiana grocery store volume including delicatessen shops--no of chain grocery stores, 1928 Oct.
    - Smoking investigation among 80 men in New York Office, 1928 Oct.
    - Shoe polish business in Canada, 1928 Oct.
    - Consumer cigarette investigation in 6 large cities, 1928 Oct.
    - Consumer and dealer investigation on electrical appliances, 1928 Oct.
    - Radio investigation among consumers and dealers, 1931 Jan.
    - Office investigation La Grande prepared flour, 1931 May
    - Office investigation biscuits, 1931 May
    - Preliminary survey on baby garments, 1931 June
    - Chocolate candy bar distribution among 304 grocery stores in N.Y., 1931 July
    - Investigation among 66 women--re: consumers reaction to detachable hell lift, 1931 July
    - Office investigation razor and razor blades among men and women, 1931 Aug.
    - Report on popularity of transatlantic steamship lines, 1931 Sept.
    - Office investigation on electrical appliances, 1931 Sept.
    - Dealer survey on chocolate pudding in N.Y. City and Middleton, N.Y., 1931 July
    - Kitchen test on Vi-Tone, 1931 Oct.
    - Spotless town cleaner, 1931 Oct.
    - Plan for development of new business in drug and toilet goods field, 1931 July
    - Office investigation on Cunard Steamship Lines, 1932 Jan.
    - Report on A.C. Lawrence Leather Company, 1932 Feb.
    - Investigation to determine most popular restaurant among 56 people in New York Office, 1932 Feb.
    - Prin. types of arch-supporting shoes, 1932 Mar.
    - Market for storage batteries, 1932 Mar.
    - Normacol--Laxative, 1932 Apr.
    - Interviews with travel agencies in N.Y. City on Pacific Ocean travel, 1932 Apr.
    - Limited investigation of 5c soups, 1932 Apr.
    - Information American representatives in England regarding English companies, 1932 Apr.
    - Investigation on ginger ale, 1932 May
    - Magazine survey in Rochester N.Y. (Good House Keeping), 1932 Apr.
    - Smoking test of 15c and 10c cigarettes, 1932 Oct.
    - Savings account survey, 1932 Aug.
    - Popular types--Shade and brands of rouge and lipstick, 1932 Aug.
    - Ice cream data, 1932 Oct.
    - Office investigation Durham Duplex razors, 1932 Oct.
    - Blindfold test to show preference for different brands of 10c cigarettes, 1932 Nov.
    - Effect of price reductions on sales of nationally advertised brands, 1932 Dec.
    - Office investigation Windolene, 1932 Dec.
    - Test of Jaxonette shampoo cloth, 1933 Jan.
    - Report on fresh dates, 1933 Jan.
    - Memorandum on alternative methods of distribution for Carling's ale within U.S., 1933 Apr.
    - Preliminary survey of household cleanser market, 1933 Apr.
    - Home use of household deodorants, 1933 May
    - Preliminary investigations among consumers in N.Y. and Providence, 1933 Mar.
    - Coca-Cola office and consumer survey, 1933 June
    - Consumer investigation of market for bluing and allied products, 1933 July
    - Office investigation--Sugar, 1933 July
    - Investigation of market for Scalptone, 1933 July
    - Pre investigation of Coca-Cola--Consumption of boys 10 to 18 years, 1933 July
    - Limited investigation of Coca-Cola in Charleston and Gaffney S.C., 1933 Aug.
    - Household cleanser test, 1933 Sept.
    - Import and export figures on sardines, 1933 Sept.
    - Analysis of attitude of state departments of education and natural health organizations toward Coca-Cola, 1933 Sept.
    - Consumer survey in 4 cities toward Coca-Cola, 1933 Sept.
    - JWT office test with free Coca-Cola, 1933 Sept.
    - Consumer investigation on remedies used for indigestion and other common ailments, 1933 Sept.
    - The domestic oil burner industry, 1933 Sept.
    - Analysis of Coca-Cola 1933 media, 1933 Nov.
    - Test of consumer attitude toward health properties of Coca-Cola, 1933 Nov.
    - The Coca-Cola problem (Continued on reel #51), 1933 Nov.
    - Test of Robinsons Patent Barley--Barley water (Continued on reel #51), 1933 Dec.
    - Consumer investigation on soda crackers (Continued on reel #51), 1934 Jan.
    - Comparative analysis--JWT and McCann-Erickson (Continued on reel #51), 1934 Feb.
    - Investigation on Phillip's soup (Continued on reel #51), 1934 Feb.
    - Coca-Cola problem, 1933 Nov. (Reel 51)
    - Test of Robinson's Patent Barley--Barley water, 1933 Dec.
    - Consumer investigation on soda crackers, 1934 Jan.
    - Comparative analysis--JWT and McCann-Erickson, 1934 Feb.
    - Investigation on Phillip's soup, 1934 Feb.
    - Limited dealer investigation of bake lining market in Westchester County, 1934 June
    - Investigation among 40 auto dealers to determine attitude toward national advertising, 1934 June
    - Expansion of Coca-Cola sales, 1934 June
    - Office investigation--Chevrolet, 1934 June
    - Consumer asked to name passenger cars made by General Motors, 1934 July
    - US market for Intourists, Inc., 1934 July
    - Case study of trends in fruit consumption, 1934 July
    - Root beer survey and consumer survey of drinking habits--Non-intoxicating beverages and beers, 1934 Mar.
    - Current brand trends in consumption of cigarettes, 1934 Mar.
    - Trend of sale and distribution in rubber sundries, 1932 Apr.
    - General information on sugar, 1932 Apr.
    - Limited investigation with Plymouth, Ford and Chevrolet dealers, 1932 Feb.
    - Expansion of Coca-Cola sales, 1934 Sept.
    - Coca-Cola tests, 1934 Oct.
    - Suggested areas and newspaper costs for tests of 2 types of copy, 1934 Oct.
    - Coca-Cola versus Pepsi-Cola test, 1934 Nov.
    - Consumer investigation of headache remedies, 1934 Nov.
    - Limited investigation of parent's attitude toward safety of automobiles, 1934 Nov.
    - Cigarette smell tests (Blind), 1935 Jan.
    - Office investigation on what people consider leading automobile company, 1935 Feb.
    - Office investigation on milk bath, 1935 Apr.
    - Can you tell the brand of cigarettes by taste?, 1935 June
    - Study of Old Gold market problem, 1935 June
    - Indication of Frigidaire position in consumer preference, 1935 July
    - Supplementary information secured from Frigidaire, 1935 Aug.
    - Preliminary tabulation of refrigerator survey, 1935 Sept.
    - Final report on refrigerator survey, 1935 Sept.
    - Investigation among pipe smokers--also information on snuff, tobacco, Inc., 1935 Sept.
    - Test among 72 men of new Enders razor (See Durham Duplex)(See also reel #220), 1935 Oct.
    - Study of market potentialities for Spry (Rubbing alcohol), 1935 Dec.
    - Market and media study for Woolworth, 1936 Jan.
    - Relative popularity of fruits--Juices and fruit dishes, 1936 Aug.
    - Basic facts on anthracite coal industry, 1936 July
    - Total assets and earnings of Artloom and Bigelow-Sanford companies, 1936 Apr.
    - Investigation in department stores and specialty shops on advertised brands of stockings, 1936 May
    - Investigation of mentholated cigarettes, 1936 May
    - Investigation in Macy's on iceboxes, 1936 July
    - Office investigation--Graham crackers and toasted breads, 1936 July
    - Medicine cabinet survey--St. Louis Office, 1936 Sept.
    - Consumer and dealer survey on spray alcohol--Conducted by Bay Rubbing Apprentice Group, 1937 Jan.
    - Office check on suggested Lucidin car card--Conducted by Bay Rubbing Apprentice Group, 1937 Mar.
    - Test of Vip-Vi-Tone, Ovaltine and Toddy, 1936 Oct.
    - Preliminary discussion of findings--Universal Pictures Corporation, 1936 Dec.
    - Kitchen test on Tendra, 1937 Jan.
    - Consumer lettuce survey in N.Y., 1937 Jan.
    - US Playing Card Company, 1937 Jan. (Reel 52)
    - Leading insurance companies other than life, 1937 Feb.
    - Travel--Office investigation, 1937 May
    - McCall's magazine readers--Survey of food eaters, 1937 June
    - Hair preparation tonics, 1937 July
    - House paints--N. Dakota, 1935
    - FW Woolworth Company--N.J. survey, 1937 Aug.
    - House paint (outside) dealer, 1937 Oct.
    - Canned salmon industry, 1937 Oct.
    - New York market survey--NYU Bureau for Newspaper Ad Managers Assn., 1937 Oct.
    - New England confectionery candy, 1938 May
    - Norfolk Va. (vacation) office investigation, 1928 Aug.
    - Permatit--Analysis of population, etc., 1931 Feb.
    - Permatit--Estimated market for water softening units, 1932 Sept.
    - Electrical refrigerators and oil burners--Sales and advertising, 1921-1931
    - Royal types vs. copper engravings--Study, 1929 Oct.
    - Viyelia yarn, 1932 Aug.
    - Peters chocolate (Nestlé's cocoa)--Various investigations, 1924-1932
    - JC Penney Company--Various investigations, 1937 Mar.-May
    - Pennsylvania RR, 1931 May-1932 Nov.
    - Three leading railroads--Newspaper and magazine advertising, 1931 Nov.
    - Shampoos, 1932 Aug.
    - 3 leading RR--Newspaper and magazine advertising, 1932 June, Aug.
    - Passenger transportation--Investigation public attitude, 1932 Jan.-Mar., Nov.
    - Travel survey, N.J. Pa. RR, 1933 Jan.
    - Pa. RR--Office investigation executives--Newspaper and magazine advertising, 1926 June
    - Leading RRs--Analysis, 1930 July
    - Peace dale knitting, yarn investigation, 1923 Sept.
    - Peace dale knitting, questionnaire, 1924 May
    - Penick and Ford--Molasses and maple syrup investigation, 1928-1933
    - Oils (Salad and cooking) investigations New Orleans, etc., 1924 Apr.
    - Panama Pacific, ad income, 1935 July
    - Panama Pacific, Hungarian travel, 1935 Aug.
    - Panama Pacific, advertising plan, 1935 Dec.
    - Odorono--Various investigations, 1934 Aug.-Nov.
    - Chocolate products and how made--W. K. Wallbridge (Vice--Pres.), 1934
    - Lamont-Corliss and Company--Croquettes, 1925 Aug.-Dec.
    - Peter's milk chocolate--Conference, 1919 June, 1925
    - Peter's milk chocolate--Investigation, 1922 July
  - Pond's Extract Company
    - Pond's extract Company--Various investigations, 1927 June-Nov.
    - Pond's extract Company--Various investigations, 1928 Dec.-1930
    - Pond's extract Company--Various investigations, 1933